interapptive.com 2016-05-21

# ShipWorks Privacy Policy

### Personal Information

“Personal Information” is information that identifies you as an individual. When you create an account on a Interapptive or ShipWorks websites, participate in a promotional activity, participate in our forums and message boards, or contact our product support, we may collect a variety of Personal Information, which depending on the circumstances may include your name, mailing address, phone number, email address and payment card information. We may use the Personal Information about you for communications to provide you with the products and services you requested, to communicate with you about your account, to give you important information about the software, or send you offers and promotions about our products and applications. We urge you to exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose Personal Information, or any other information, on our sites. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU VOLUNTARILY DISCLOSE THROUGH THE SITES.

### Email Addresses

We will never give your email address to anyone for any reason. We hate spam just as much as you do. 

### IP Addresses

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site and gather broad demographic information for aggregated used. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a tiny file that stores personal preferences and user data, but in no way does this tell us who you are. We use cookies as part of our authentication system when you login to your account. If you select the “remember me” option when logging in, our site will set a cookie so that you do not have to login again the next time you visit the ShipWorks or Interapptive website.

While both of these activities depend on the use of a “cookie,” visitors to this site always have the option of disabling cookies in their web browser. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. 

We may use cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIF’s or other similar tools on our websites or in our email messages. These technologies help Interapptive and ShipWorks keep track of your movements within our sites, measure the effectiveness of advertisements, and compile aggregate statistics about site usage and response rates. They also help you to more smoothly navigate our websites. In addition, we use Google Analytics as a method of tracking site statistics and user behavior on many of our sites. We may also engage one or more third party service providers to serve online advertisements on our behalf, such as Google AdWords and AdWords remarketing. These third party services may use a pixel tag to collect anonymous information about your visits to sites, and they may use that information to target advertisements for goods and services. This information is collected anonymously, in a manner that does not personally identify you. For more information regarding this practice and to opt-out of such collection and use of this information by our third party service providers, please see Networkadvertising.org. If you do not want information collected through the use of these technologies there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline many of these technologies, or to be given the choice of declining or accepting them. In addition, you may be able to opt out of customized Google Display Network ads by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager (http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/), and the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on (http://www.google.ca/ads/preferences/plugin/). Your use of this website without opting out means that you understand and agree to data collection to provide you with remarketing ads using GA and cookies from other third party vendors based on your prior visits to this website and elsewhere on the Internet. 

### Social Media

Certain of our sites may include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and they might set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our sites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing the feature. Please note that we are not responsible for the collection, usage and disclosure policies and practices (including the data security practices) of other organizations, such as Facebook, Apple, Google, Microsoft, or any other app, social media platform or wireless service provider. 

### Information Dissemination

None of the information that is collected by this web site is rented or sold to any 3rd parties for any purpose. Limited information may be shared with a 3rd party that has partnered with Interapptive and/or ShipWorks if that information is protected under a confidentiality agreement with that 3rd party and is used only as a part of providing the ShipWorks service to the customer. 

### Links to Other Sites

Interapptive expects its partners and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners and affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. 

### Security

This web site has security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and/or alteration of the information that you provide. Furthermore, we have taken every precaution technically possible to prevent any unauthorized access to the contents of this web server. 

### Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to support@shipworks.com or by mail to: ShipWorks, One Memorial Drive, 20th Floor, St. Louis, MO 63102.
